<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-04T21:31:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">SorceRawr</title><subtitle>The Source of the best Media in the Matrix.</subtitle><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><entry><title type="html">Games</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/2021/07/03/Games.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Games" /><published>2021-07-03T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-07-03T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/2021/07/03/Games</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/2021/07/03/Games.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2021/07/03/Games.html&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/unused-energy-24.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Games I’m currently interested in&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/games1.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;broken image: games 1 &quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/games2.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;broken image: games 2 &quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/games3.png&quot; alt=&quot;broken image: games 3 &quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Taking The Genie Out Of The Bottle</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/genie" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Taking The Genie Out Of The Bottle" /><published>2021-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-07-01T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Taking-the-Genie-Out-of-the-Bottle</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/genie">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/genie&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/unused-energy-13.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to save you some time. You have a genie in a bottle. You always have. You probably believe that
wishes don’t come true, because when you were a child, you watched people pray, and you watched their prayers go unanswered.
This may come as a surprise, but those same people who don’t know how to tie their own shoes, they also don’t know how to pray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to skip past narratives and we’ll just assume that you, walking along the side of a road, discovered a bottle with a genie in it,
and you’re ready to use it. First we need to answer a glaring question. Where is the 1969 Pontiac Firebird you wished for?
Well, as far as I understand it, your genie may not be able to give you your brand new car, or, perhaps your wish is actually so terrible for the
outcome of your life that he has just pretended he didn’t hear that one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are going to assume the defining characteristic of your genie. Your genie is good, and by good I mean favorable. Why would we assume this?
This is because you, ‘the wisher’, are making a wish that you intend to have a favorable outcome. This means that you trust that the genie you
are wishing to would grant a wish that would favor you. You are then, wishing to a good genie, a genie that you trust wants to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This defining characteristic matters because the entity we are dealing with that concerns goodness is only going to be connected to, associated with,
that in his domain. It’s fairly possible that your genie may not even be able to &lt;em&gt;hear&lt;/em&gt; wishes that fall outside of goodness. This is about the time
when you tell me that there is no such thing as the archaic dualistic concept of ‘Good or Evil’, you’ve intellectually transcended such concepts.
Now take three steps back, and leave your philosophy at the door. You’re going to need to identify the difference in order to work with this genie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good in this context is what is good for your soul, what grows and nurtures it rather than withers and harms it. A main theme here is that we do not
always aspire towards what is actually good for us. This isn’t a bad thing, it’s just that the fulfillment our desires often do not grant what we had hoped for. Let’s say I really want that Pontiac, because it will make me feel proud and confident about myself. Feeling proud and confident are good feelings, these &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; good things. There’s also nothing wrong with a car. It’s just that the car will not grant those emotional feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[ Upon watching &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DnPmg0R1M04&amp;amp;lc&quot;&gt;this documentary&lt;/a&gt; that shows how we were mass manipulated reprogrammed to identify the essence of our selves with materialism, you might ask yourself if anyone believed they could fulfill their desires with consumerism before the 1900s.]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve established that the genie will not grant you something you wish for that does not actually grant the emotional desire you are seeking. The genie will grant that which it is associated with, goodness. So let’s identify what this may include. Here are the Christian and Catholic fruits of the spirit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/fruit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;broken image: Charity Joy Peace Patience Benignity Goodness Longanimity Mildness Faith Modesty Continency Chastity&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/spiritfruit.png&quot; alt=&quot;broken image: But the fruit of the spirit is love, joy, peace, patience, kindness, goodness, faithfulness, gentleness, self-control; against such things there is no law. Galatians 5:22-23&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something important here is that there are principles in this world that can hinder, interfere with your ability to attain a great many things. “Against such things there is no law”, means that there is no principle preventing you from accessing the things of this nature. In a videogame, we might call this a kind of cheat code, such as exploiting an ‘infinite money glitch’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goodness may seem to be a small constrictive box from which to operate in until you see it open up, and see that goodness contains every attribute you most desire. Wisdom, resilience, confidence, strength, clarity, focus, resoluteness, all that man aspires towards. Below are Benjamin Franklin’s famous virtues I often share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/benjaminvirtue.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Broken image: Temperance Silence Order Resolution Frugality Industry Sincerity Justice Moderation Cleanliness Chastity Tranquility Humility&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are simply inspiration, as again you can start with the virtues that you most desire to have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now what if your wish is for something like the power to hurt others? You do you, but now you’re dealing with a different genie. You’re now dealing with an entity that may help you harm others, but will also inevitably harm and destroy you, as that is the nature of the force which you have chosen to barter with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back to our good genie, we can wish for good virtues, and then follow a process with which to receive these wishes. Now why would I want these virtues?
Anyone who has played an RPG has come to learn that the Skill Points they put into skills greatly affects the outcome of the entire game, even often those chosen at the very start.&lt;br /&gt;
These skills are your fruit, and the fruits you plant are the fruits that grow and come out of you. Those fruits equate to value, and the richer of a
person you are, the more fruit you have, the more true authentic value you have, not the false sense of value our egos attempt to build up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to say it is that if you want something, you invest in yourself becoming the kind of person who would attain that thing. You become who you need to be in order to attain it, because only the person qualified to obtain something will obtain it. You would need to become that person.
You become the character with the skills and attributes needed to take on a journey.
You become the kind of person who possesses the virtues necessary to get what you want out of life.
So use the infinite points glitch and max out your skill points to unlimited, “Charisma 99+”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most important paragraph of this read, and this is the required process in working with a genie in a bottle.
0(optional). Ask the genie what you should wish for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make your wish.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have faith and the understanding that you will be granted this wish.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set this wish as your focus, write it down, think about it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Seek out to find your answered wish. You already know your wish has been answered, now you just have to find it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s can be so easy to use this process that it is as if you are being carried and hardly even an active participant, as long as you move forward
and continue to seek, you move towards it. That’s one of the secrets, you’re always moving towards something, whether it be a good thing or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The genie, however you may call it or choose to think of it, is something you should take seriously, because if you don’t take it seriously, why the hell should any of this take you seriously? Seeking is an active process. It means challenging yourself. It means learning and googling and reading. It means participating in your own life for your own behalf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s about all I can advise for a generalization on the topic. If you’re curious about what I do with this and have come to find personally, read on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My top and target wish is always Wisdom. This is because wisdom is valuable to me and my life and the lives of others entirely by its lonesome.
It’s because Wisdom can grant the wisdom to know what to wish for. This is a valid wish. You can pray to ask what to pray for. You can ask what
should my desires be. You can ask what would truly help you.
Wisdom says that at any time, you cannot see the whole picture from the limited awareness that you are stuck in in time, and for this reason you cannot see the best possible possibility of outcome for your life, it is unimaginable to you. The answer to what is the best possible outcome is an answer that lies outside of yourself, and that is why you must wish for this unknowable possibility and ask for it to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, a major part of wishes, faith and prayers is trusting that a force that knows more than you is benevolent and wishes to give you the best possibility of outcome, that is if what you want is the best possibility of outcome. As you might be able to see, this requires surrendering the outcome. It requires making your wish more vague and abstract, less concrete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you experiment with prayer what you will find is that you can make many concrete wishes come true, and like the old adage, “Be careful what you wish for”, you will learn that getting your concrete wish answered and controlling the outcome does not lead to a desirable outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wisdom prays for the best outcome, and the best blessings, better virtues, better focuses, better perspectives, better than oneself can imagine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Wisdom, I seek out creativity, because honestly that’s all I really give a fuck about these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A last warning on the distinction between wishful thinking and working with these principles. Wishful thinking is simply delusion, fantasy, imagination that will not come into form, when you do not participate. Another perspective to take is that you will always move toward what you want most. You may want security and comfort more than the desire you wish for, and so you will not have the desire you wish for, because you move towards
what you desire most. Remember Benjamin Franklin’s virtues? He moved towards them. Below was his calendar to track virtues. By tracking virtues, he focused on virtues. By focusing on them, he moved towards them to become who he aspired to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/benjamincalendar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Broken image: Benjamin Franklin's calendar tracking virtues with X crossmarks for each day he demonstrated these virtues in his life by day of the week&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Note Neverending</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/noteneverending" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note Neverending" /><published>2021-06-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Notes-Neverending</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/noteneverending">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/noteneverending&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/unused-energy-02.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pouring into a data stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://sorcerawr.com/notebook&quot;&gt;books and resources from these notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
books
Alchemist --
Dickinson --
Happiness Project --
Big Magic --
Septuagint  --
Owning Your Own Shadow --
Inner Gold --
Century of the Self
Ayla
Poetry Foundation

Brene Brown


&lt;!-- I should add amazon links to every book on here! --&gt;
&lt;link href=&quot;https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Playfair+Display&amp;amp;display=swap&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; /&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
#note {

  background-color: #E4D4C8;
  font-size: 1.5em;
  color: black;
  font-family: 'Playfair Display', serif;
  line-height: 1.5;
  letter-spacing: .6px;
}
#notetext {
  text-align: left;
  margin-left: 10px;

}
#main {

    background-image: url(/img/paper2.png);
    background-repeat: repeat;

}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;note&quot;&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;notetext&quot;&gt;
&lt;!-- # A collection of my words from this year is at moti &gt; chaos &gt; words 2021 --&gt;
&lt;!-- make this beautiful like a journal E4D4C8 D2B48C--&gt;


&lt;h2&gt; Big Magic I &lt;/h2&gt;

You do not need a permission slip from the principal's office to live a creative life. &lt;br /&gt;
Or if you do worry that you need a permission slip--- &lt;br /&gt;
THERE, I just gave it to you. &lt;br /&gt;
I just wrote it on the back of an old shopping list. &lt;br /&gt;
Consider yourself fully accredited. &lt;br /&gt;
Now go make something. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Paradox, It matters./It doesn't matter.&lt;br /&gt;
Build space in your head for this paradox &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;My creative expression must be the most important thing in the world to me (if I am to live artistically), and it also must not matter to me at all (if I am to live sanely)&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'It ain't what they call you, it's what you answer to' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
What a wonderful life I've had. I only wish I'd realized it sooner. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;


&lt;h2&gt; Dickinson &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;
Will there really be a &quot;Morning&quot;?
Is there such a thing as &quot;Day&quot;?
Could I see it from the mountains
If I were as tall as they?

Has it feet like Water lilies?
Has it feathers like a Bird?
Is it brought from famous countries
Of which I have never heard?

Oh some Scholar! Oh some Sailor!
Oh some Wise Man from the skies!
Where to tell a little Pilgrim
Where the place called &quot;Morning&quot; lies!
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Dickinson &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;
A darting fear - a pomp - a tear -
A waking on a morn
To find that what one waked for
Inhales the different dawn.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt; Happiness Project I &lt;/h2&gt;

That's me, I thought, there I am. I have.. a cell phone.. alarm clock.. apartment.. neighborhood.. This is my life..&lt;br /&gt;
I was suffering from a midlife malaise--a recurrent sense of discontent and almost feeling of disbelief. &quot;Can this be me?&quot; I'd wonder. &lt;br /&gt;

&quot;Is this really it? Yep, this is it.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I had everything I could possibly want, yet I was failing to appreciate it. I too often failed to comprehend the splendor of what I had.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Colette: 'What a wonderful life I've had! I only wish I'd realized it sooner.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

How could I set a higher standard for myself as a wife, a mother, a writer, a friend? How could I let go of everyday annoyances to keep a larger, more transcendent perspective?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The opposite of happiness is unhappiness, not depression. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
 More likely to make progress with..concrete, measurable actions..structured accountability + positive reinforcement. &lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;br /&gt;
Unconscious mind does crucial work in forming judgements, motives, and feelings outside our awareness or conscious control, and one factor that influences the work of the unconscious is the
&quot;accessibility of information&quot;, or the ease at which it comes to mind. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Info that is recalled often or used is easier to retrieve and therefore energized..&lt;br /&gt;
by reminding myself of certain goals and ideas, I could keep them more active in my mind. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

[she identified &quot;resolutions&quot; she wanted to address, (relationships world perspective attitude work play passion energy money mindfulness), then found overarching
principles around these emerge.]&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

Epicurus wrote, &quot;We must exercise ourselves in the things which bring happiness, since, if that be present, we have everything, and, if that be absent, all our actions are directed towards
attaining it.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Though I didn't realize this immediately--I started my happiness project because I wanted to prepare..for adversity--to develop the self-discipline and the mental habits to deal with a bad thing
when it happened. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Dickinson &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;

Perhaps the &quot;Kingdom of Heaven's&quot; changed -
I hope the &quot;Children&quot; there
Won't be &quot;new fashioned&quot; when I come -
And laugh at me - and stare -

I hope the Father in the skies
Will lift his little girl -
Old fashioned - naughty - everything
Over the stile of &quot;Pearl.&quot;

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Sirach &lt;/h2&gt;

How the little is sufficient for a disciplined person.. - 34:17 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Become skillful in all your deeds.. 34:22 &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt; Dickinson &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;

&quot;If pain for peace prepares
Lo, what &quot;Augustan&quot; years
Can the Anemones
Be reckoned up?

If night stands first - then noon
To gird us for the sun,
What gaze!

When from a thousand skies
On our developed eyes
Noons blaze! &quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt; Owning Your Own Shadow &lt;/h2&gt;

'Beauty (or worth) is in the eyes of the beholder' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Gold in the Shadow: &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There are two shadows: 1 the dark side of the ego, which is carefully hidden from itself and which
the ego will not acknowledge unless forced to by life's difficulties, and (2) that which has been
repressed in us lest it interfere with our egocentricity and, however devilish it may seem, is basically
connected to the Self. &lt;br /&gt;
In a showdown God (Self) favors the shadow over the ego, for the shadow, with all of its dangerousness,
is closer to the center and more genuine.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

People are as frightened of their capacity for nobility as of their darkest sides. &lt;br /&gt;
If you find the gold in someone who will resist it to the last ounce of his strength. &lt;br /&gt;
This is why we engage in hero-worship so often. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;

Our hero worshipping capacity is pure shadow, our finest qualities are refused and laid on another. &lt;br /&gt;
Todays hero is tomorrows character. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

As the shadow is drawn up into consciousness, it becomes softer, more pliable, more gentle. &lt;br /&gt;
..neither ego nor shadow can be redeemed unless its twin is transformed.. &lt;br /&gt;
rubbing together..this is nothing less than healing the split between heaven and hell. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'If we can learn to love the inner enemy, then there is a chance of loving - and redeeming - the outer one.' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;When we can face our inner heaven and our inner hell, this is the highest form of creativity.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
To be in the presence of another's shadow and not reply is nothing short of genius.
No one has the right to dump his shadow on you, and you have the right to self protection. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Most people have to work very hard to throw off their parent's shadow &lt;br /&gt;
If a parent lays his shadow on a young child, that splits the personality of the child &lt;br /&gt;
and sets the ego-shadow warfare into motion. When that child grows up, he will have a large shadow to cope with &lt;br /&gt;
and also have the tendency to put that shadow upon his own children. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'..Acts will have an equal weight on opposite side of scale...
we can be aware of this dynamic and make a conscious gesture to compensate for it..' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

The unconscious cannot tell the difference between a 'real' act and a symbolic one &lt;br /&gt;
[which means we can pay out that darkness in a symbolic way
short story or active imagination mentioned, mentions another book he wrote,
Inner Work: Using Dreams and Active Imagination for Personal Growth.] &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'Had any terrible successes lately?' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There is a broader sense of creativity that folds the darkness into the finished
product and finds fulfillment in the shadow. This is pure genius. Its attributes
are wholeness, health, and holiness,
and saintness in the original meaning of the word, a full embracing of humanity. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

The more refined our conscious personality, the more shadow we have built
up on the other side. &lt;br /&gt;
Jung's insight, the ego and shadow come from the same source and exactly balance each other. &lt;br /&gt;
To make light is to make shadow; one cannot exist without the other.

To own one's shadow is to reach an holy place- an inner center--&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Century of the Self &lt;/h2&gt;

Bernes made up his own title..field..idea..'public relations' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Sirach &lt;/h2&gt;

The wise in word will make himself beloved. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The heart of the stupid is in their mouth, but the mouth of the wise is in their heart. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
And he put his eye upon their hearts &lt;br /&gt;
to show them the splendor of his works.. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;h2&gt; Poetry Foundation &lt;/h2&gt;

“Poetry redeems from decay the visitations of the divinity in man.” The poem is a genie that comes out of the bottle to liberate the reader’s imagination, the divinity within. &lt;br /&gt;
The writer and the reader make meaning together. The poet who calls on help from the heavenly muse also does so on behalf of the imaginative reader. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

[W.S. Merwin, for example, remembers his teacher John Berryman giving him advice in the years just after the Second World War:] &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;

he suggested I pray to the Muse
get down on my knees and pray
right there in the corner and he
said he meant it literally

[Berryman also said that]

the great presence
that permitted everything and transmuted it
in poetry was passion
passion was genius and he praised movement and invention
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Tara Brach &lt;/h2&gt;

When you see them in their inner beauty and goodness you transform and create. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

What's standing between me and my own goodness? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Protecting my purity for years like the buddha statue covered in clay.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

See how much they must be judging themselves, how sad.. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Ayla &lt;/h2&gt;


Try on different things, take on a different self &lt;br /&gt;
Take on another essence, or like an accent, pretend &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Culture of dampening our light &lt;br /&gt;
Culture that says we arent supposed to be in a state of wonder at all times, &lt;br /&gt;
at the magnificence of whats going on around us &lt;br /&gt;
and to be in a state of wonder about our emotions &lt;br /&gt;
and about the parts of our planet that also need healing &lt;br /&gt;
doesn't want us to stay in a state of wonder, &lt;br /&gt;
there is power in our wonder &lt;br /&gt;
there is power in our innocent eyes looking up and being curious &lt;br /&gt;
there is power in wondering in awe at pain and destruction &lt;br /&gt;
when we approach these things that might be challenging, we approach with curiosity and wonder &lt;br /&gt;
it changes how we talk about it, how we understand it, how a creation will be about it &lt;br /&gt;
to put on a different lens that is very curious about life and looking at the details &lt;br /&gt;
and wanting to understand more about why things are the way it is and &lt;br /&gt;
how do things feel like and come up new words and plant these seeds that create flowers of detail and bring us into
a new environment, a place we want to bring people. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
We inspire change by touching on the awe of the thing we want to observe. When we exalt and praise what is necessary
and essential for life, we bring others into our world, and we give them a pair of binoculars to look at the marvelous things
that we're seeing, &lt;br /&gt;
How can you not want to protect the planet when you see how amazing it is?&lt;br /&gt;
How can you not want to protect a forest when it brings you into a feeling or makes..
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Use detail to bring each other into a world a whole universe we are creating..&lt;br /&gt;
Creating more experiences in life and in your self where we are open.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Wrap our shame in a hug, wrap the whole experience in a hug, our energetic embrace, accept it, love ourselves with whatever's going on in there.. &lt;br /&gt;
Dropping the resistance, loving myself just as I am for everything I'm feeling right now. &lt;br /&gt;
sing to the shame, &lt;br /&gt;
or ask it what its afraid of, what it needs. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In many traditions, it is no longer a gift if you record it, to where you were intending it.. &lt;br /&gt;
so when you record it, it freezes it.. &lt;br /&gt;
that's why a lot of the old spells were not recorded..
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Magic Field.. &lt;br /&gt;
take a few deep breaths &lt;br /&gt;
feel into your energy field &lt;br /&gt;
you can tune into how close or far it is, right near your skin or very far away, &lt;br /&gt;
parts of it might be in the past or future &lt;br /&gt;
don't really have to even do anything, intend that your energy body comes to about 4 feet of you. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
play with it, moving it out and in until you move it about 4-5ish feet from your body &lt;br /&gt;
and with your breath you're going to feel into your heart first, tune into the radiance of your heart, &lt;br /&gt;
like a lightbulb inside your heart &lt;br /&gt;
and you're going to feel that light fill through every cell in your body through all of your atoms, &lt;br /&gt;
expanding with your breath &lt;br /&gt;
might feel tingly, or soft &lt;br /&gt;
and just expand that light outside your skin, farther farther, until it is permeating that whole energy field
around you. &lt;br /&gt;
And just take a few deep breaths charging it up, with more light, or love, &lt;br /&gt;
however it feels right to you &lt;br /&gt;
and you're going to just feel how that light and that love that is this vital energy &lt;br /&gt;
and you're just going to send beams of love into your cells, into your body, into your throat &lt;br /&gt;
into all the chakras, your organs, every cell, every single cell &lt;br /&gt;
sending all your love and gratitude &lt;br /&gt;
and then still feeling that energy radiating in you, you can start to beam, it might already be beaming &lt;br /&gt;
but feel the beam, feel the emanation that's coming from you, &lt;br /&gt;
light emitted from your being, so you're a beacon, &lt;br /&gt;
that love, that love, that vital force is a beacon &lt;br /&gt;
and you can keep that, keep that feeling, you can open your eyes but keep that feeling, awareness &lt;br /&gt;
and you can keep that kind of radiant emanation energy &lt;br /&gt;
and you can turn into actually how its impossible when we're emanating this much light and love, it's impossible &lt;br /&gt;
for anything that is not love, that is not benevolent, to enter our field, because we are emanating that, &lt;br /&gt;
it can't go opposite, it's too strong. &lt;br /&gt;
I've found that this is a helpful way of making my field strong, and having a boundary without it actually being a wall,
rather it's a resonant field, &lt;br /&gt;
and anything that is not in resonance with my field cannot enter. it just wont. it cant. it's impossible. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
For me, there's also techniques you can learn to create an energetic shield around yourself and those can be helpful
too... but i've found it's actually more powerful for me to resonate and emanate into my field and nothing can enter
that's not in alignment with that. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
..So can help us remember that we're energetic beings, and actually creators, creators of  reality,
not just remembering how to create art, remembering how to be creators of our reality, every moment.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
..Send a tone, an offering to the world from the radiance of your being, &lt;br /&gt;
so you're gonna let your beacon shine really strong right now through your voice, as a vibration, &lt;br /&gt;
in this vibrational reality and you're going to send it out. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Warrior...to be a pillar means we're going to be resonating with a frequency that's going to be beneficial
to everyone around us. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'If I take the time to actually imagine the whole song or the whole orchestration around one part, and then I record my voice singing it,
it encodes all of that into it, and also leads me into the next thing and things around it, the fullness, the potential around that song,
and listening, &lt;br /&gt;
Imagining, &quot;what would be the most amazing song to hear right now? &quot; as if someone else wrote it. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Imitating, pretending you're an artist that you like. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
'You're already trying on one personality, that's you, why not try on another and just see what happens?' &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sing the shape of the sound that wants to come through, not words. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Outline a shape with sound practice. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Keep a wordbank. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Use resonance, sound meditation. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Use shielding meditation. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Write what you see/hear/taste/feel/smell/sense. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Allowing something to come through and then broadcasting is the biggest prayer we could give to others who are afraid to. &lt;br /&gt;
That is a prayer for everyone to allow more of themselves to come through. &lt;br /&gt;
So give yourself that much permission. &lt;br /&gt;
Prayer for others is much bigger than the small fear of being heard for me &lt;br /&gt;
and part of the prayer is that they *do* hear you, they hear your imperfection. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;To be love, to be an embodiment of love on this planet..&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&quot;We are love, so then we allow ourselves to be expressions of love every moment.&quot;
&quot;If you want to know how to open your creative channel, try being an embodiment of love every moment, there's nothing like that to open all the channels.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Reengage with old content for 5 mins. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Write things that describe what you're thinking about, instead of, &quot;letting go&quot;, writing things that describe that..Instead of pain, things that describe that. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sing to the stuckness itself. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Have non-limiting identification [What I do does not limit me]. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If I'm not separate from existence, then what do I have to be afraid of? &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Vessel of whatever form of creativity wants to come through, &lt;br /&gt;
its our job to catch, to always be ready to catch. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
So instead of getting to Heaven, at last — &lt;br /&gt;
I’m going, all along. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Soak in the gift of space. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
- Writing Practice 2: Do the practice above, but start with the phrase &quot;I am...&quot; Don't let the pen stop. Whenever you get caught in thinking, start the sentence over. Can also try &quot;We are..&quot; or &quot;This is...&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- Writing Practice 3: Write for 2 minutes, &lt;br /&gt;
“what do I want so deeply, but also scares me to try?” OR &lt;br /&gt;
“What am I holding back from, because I’m afraid to _____(fail / succeed / be ridiculed...)?” &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
- Writing Practice 4: - &lt;br /&gt;
Now, feel into those voices from practice 3. &lt;br /&gt;
See if they’re trying to protect you, &lt;br /&gt;
or prove something... write for 2 minutes from their voices, &lt;br /&gt;
about why they’re in your head and how they’re trying to help you. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Dickinson &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;

I died for beauty, but was scarce
Adjusted in the tomb,
When one who died for truth was lain
In an adjoining room.

He questioned softly why I failed?
“For beauty,” I replied.
“And I for truth, —the two are one;
We brethren are,” he said.

And so, as kinsmen met a night,
We talked between the rooms,
Until the moss had reached our lips,
And covered up our names.

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Brene &lt;/h2&gt;

Courage from latin cour: &quot;to speak one's mind by telling all one's heart&quot; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The courage to be imperfect.. &lt;br /&gt;
The compassion to be kind to themselves first and then to others.. &lt;br /&gt;
We can't show compassion to other people if we can't treat ourselves kindly. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
They had connection as a result of authenticity.. &lt;br /&gt;
They were willing to let go of who they thought they should be &lt;br /&gt;
in order to be who they were. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
They fully embraced vulnerability &lt;br /&gt;
They believed that what made them vulnerable made them beautiful.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Occult &lt;/h2&gt;

&quot;I have personal knowledge of more than twenty-five instances where the performance of [Enochian] magical operations based upon the Order's [i.e. Alpha et Omega's] formulae led to serious disintegrations of mind and body... &lt;br /&gt;
 Perhaps the most conspicuous example of the use of these formulas is A.C. [Aleister Crowley] himself, &lt;br /&gt;
but there are plenty of others I have personally witnessed, &lt;br /&gt;
whose personal shipwrecks have been just as complete even though their smaller tonnage, &lt;br /&gt;
so to say, makes the loss seem less deplorable...&quot;[15] &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Other &lt;/h2&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&quot;Mastering fear doesn't mean getting rid of the butterflies in your stomach. It means teaching them to fly in formation.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext&quot; data-lang=&quot;plaintext&quot;&gt;

 This is It
 and I am It
 and You are It
 and so is That
 and He is It
 and She is It
 and It is It
 and That is That
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

 &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

“I cannot remember the books I've read any more than the meals I have eaten; even so, they have made me.” ~ Ralph Waldo Emerson

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;


# Alchemist:

That's what alchemists do. They show that, when we strive to be better than we are, &lt;br /&gt;
everything around us becomes better, too. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
It is we who nourish the Soul of the World, &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Because when we love, we always strive to become better than we are.
&lt;br /&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Antilack</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/RadicalAntiLack" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Antilack" /><published>2021-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/AntiLack</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/RadicalAntiLack">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/RadicalAntiLack&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/unused-energy-07.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- change to 06-07 after testing done --&gt;

&lt;link href=&quot;https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Playfair+Display:wght@400;500&amp;amp;display=swap&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; /&gt;

&lt;link href=&quot;https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=IBM+Plex+Mono:wght@400;500&amp;amp;display=swap&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot; /&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;https://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/3.4.1/jquery.min.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
  #outputhtml { /* i dont even think this code is active wtf */
    font-family: 'Playfair Display', serif;
    color: #33302e;
    background-color: #fff1e5;
    padding: 0px 16px 0px 24px;
    font-size: 32px;
  }
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lack is a difficult dragon for our society to slay. As our system created this problem in a
radical way, the issue of destroying Lack requires a radical solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are principles in life that can be understood mentally but which are we
ourselves unable to implement into our actual lives. One of the largest of these
principles concerns gratitude. The perspective it concerns is that we are all currently
living in abundance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An introduction to this might be the statement,
“You can’t take it with you.” This is to say that you cannot take material possessions
with you after you die. This statement diminishes the value of physical treasures,
and reminds one that there are treasures more valuable than what is made of physical matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This remembrance can lead to the insight that what costs money is often replaceable,
and that the best things in life are free. That is that the joys of life, the sky and clouds,
family, love, beauty are free. The fact is that people operating within society, even homeless
populations, are living in an abundance of life’s true blessings and treasures, and often have
access to physical abundance as well. The man with a gun pointed at his head remembers this in
a second, that the gift of himself being alive and capable of breathing is priceless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It can be admittedly an annoyance to be told and reminded that we are blessed. We find that
the awareness of this being blessed barely raises our spirits and if it does bring us consolation,
it consoles for only a moment. This is because this image, this idea, is just another passing thought.
It does not reflect the construction of our mental world, and so it does not really stick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world we are programmed with is a world of need and desire, of wants and haves and dreams of
fulfillment, all future oriented. We do not spend our time thinking about all that we currently have,
only what we could have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, as is becoming well known, creates our culture of lack. A lacking person will always be lacking,
because his thoughts are lacking and he is defined by lack, driven to being close to dead or wishing he were.
A blessed person has the opposite experience, acting as a wellspring of life overflowing into every area of his attention and focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has been alive long enough to experience the world comes to see that these are not delusional perspectives of optimism or pessimism that do not reflect reality. The outside world transpires to confirm the viewpoint of a person, whether their thoughts are rich or poor. Tragedies strike the cynic for no fault of his own, and the rich fellow just happens to stumble into fortunes and successes for no apparent reason at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, what changes the life of a person is the shift of their entire world view. The filter and lens and perspective through which they see the entirety of the present moment. A lacking person does not change
simply by thinking for a moment that he is abundant. His mindset remains the same as it were a moment ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is because there are really no other branching thoughts about abundance in his mind to connect to, to continue thinking from. All of his other thoughts may be about worries and doubts and ailments and stresses
and desires. This is not someone who is thinking about love and peace and appreciation and wonder and inspiration, those things are annoying and far away and foreign to him. Unfamiliar, they have no place in his practical life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the lacking person to change, the daily thinking has to change so dramatically that there is a mental shift. What is easy to forget is that thought and thinking, is an action. We may not always intend to think,
and yet it is an action. It is a repeated action that becomes a practice. This practice every day becomes who we are and what we are, and we have become what we think about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can be a lacking person if I choose to practice thinking about being lacking every day. Imagine how much I can hurt myself by practicing thinking self destructive and negative thoughts every day, and imagine how many people are practicing this right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The unfortunate part, we know that thinking things over and over doesn’t make us believe them and doesn’t make it stick. A lot of us don’t have the willpower to do such a mental exercise anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, we do not need to put effort into having certain thoughts at all. We only have to set our focus on a target, and from that focus thoughts arise in us. All one has to do is keep
choosing this focus until that focus becomes familiar. What is familiar to us is the comfort zone we tend to drift towards even when we forget our goals and intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus to get out of the lacking worldview and into abundance is gratitude. Gratitude is a kind of practice of an action because it is not simply a thought, it is a thought accompanied by feeling. These kinds of thoughts, charged with emotion, are more powerful than dead repetition, and have the power to shift what our world looks and feels like, into another worldview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do this, choose something to feel grateful for, then set the Intention to feel thankful for the thing. The intention is the only important part, and that is enough to generate the thankfulness. This thankfulness is Appreciation, to appreciate the value of something that you are grateful is here and not lost. This feeling is the feeling that something is wonderful, remarkable, exciting, interesting. If this absolutely does not work for you in the slightest, then imagine what it would feel like to feel such feelings. Pretend that it is marvelous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choose your heartbeat, or your breath, or water, or light, or air to be grateful for, and look into its true value. We tend to diminish the value of incredibly important gifts of life because of
their vast abundance and because we do not expect them to leave us. However, there is no guarantee that you will have another breath after this moment at all. This precious gift and many others
are allowing you to experience a world rich with sensation, beauty, emotion, wonder, and deeper phenomena if you begin to search for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developing appreciation through gratitude is the first area to grow your awareness of a world of abundance. It can be said that while you are the one practicing gratitude,
it is not you who opens up your awareness to appreciation, your awareness opens and your perspective widens without you doing anything at all. When you see this other reality,
and color fills your world, and you become rich, you can explore and open up to the other fruits of the heart, the treasures that come from goodness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as worry, doubt, anxiety, fear, perpetuate and together create one reality, so too is another reality composed of its own elements that can be lived in. When you fall out of the better reality
again, just remember the gate that will let you enter through again. The gate is gratitude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember also that to achieve this feat of appreciation is to change who you are. You become a person who appreciates. People who appreciate life, well, they tend to be rich, because they know
they are already rich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to practice gratitude until it opens us up to the reality of abundance. My preferred method is creating what I like to call a Book of Power, containing in it ‘gratitude prayers’ to God and divinity on pen and paper. This exercise and gratitude in general help keep in mind what you are being appreciative of. There is more to appreciate in that which has more value,
that which is good, and full of life. There is plenty to appreciate in material items like cars and suits, but not on the depth and level that will open your eyes up to a deeper world of blessing.
This mindful selection is what will guide your focus into far greater blessings than you ever realized you could attain, especially after you come to realize that if you thank god for the
good virtues you want and technically already possess [examples: confidence, strength, wisdom], you will see those good virtues come out of you, as if to confirm what you had thanked God for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The button below randomizes and mashes together some of the prayers from my last Book of Power, to give an example of what kinds of gratitude prayers are possible to write.
If you can write 10 of these a day, focus your intention to feel appreciation for it, it will shift your experience of this wonderful life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt; &lt;!-- test without this div also to see output!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! --&gt;
&lt;button id=&quot;firebutton&quot; onclick=&quot;fire()&quot;&gt; Generate Gratitude &lt;/button&gt;

&lt;p id=&quot;outputhtml&quot;&gt; Good Day! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
wordList = [
&quot;Shaping my Life and my Being as an Expressive and Beautiful Piece of Art&quot;,
&quot;Reciprocation&quot;,
&quot;Allowing Me to Share so Much&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Experience these deep expressive emotions&quot;,
&quot;Connecting my Heart to Light&quot;,
&quot;feeding me in Spirit&quot;,
&quot;Light&quot;,
&quot;Life&quot;,
&quot;this Beautiful Life&quot;,
&quot;Living&quot;,
&quot;Love&quot;,
&quot;this Love&quot;,
&quot;Spirit&quot;,
&quot;Possibility&quot;,
&quot;Possibilities&quot;,
&quot;the Beautiful&quot;,
&quot;Infinite Beauty&quot;,
&quot;Endless Abundance&quot;,
&quot;Blessings&quot;,
&quot;Teachings&quot;,
&quot;every Moment&quot;,
&quot;Leading&quot;,
&quot;Leading me to Choose Love&quot;,
&quot;Guiding&quot;,
&quot;Showing&quot;,
&quot;Continuing&quot;,
&quot;Creating&quot;,
&quot;Creation&quot;,
&quot;Creating me&quot;,
&quot;Allowing&quot;,
&quot;Connecting&quot;,
&quot;Connection&quot;,
&quot;Strength&quot;,
&quot;Strengthening&quot;,
&quot;Giving&quot;,
&quot;Wisdom&quot;,
&quot;Empowering&quot;,
&quot;Empowerment&quot;,
&quot;Voice&quot;,
&quot;Safety&quot;,
&quot;Protecting&quot;,
&quot;Protection&quot;,
&quot;Rest&quot;,
&quot;Resting&quot;,
&quot;Still&quot;,
&quot;Stillness&quot;,
&quot;Comfort&quot;,
&quot;Comforting&quot;,
&quot;Peace&quot;,
&quot;Peacefulness&quot;,
&quot;Stability&quot;,
&quot;Kindness&quot;,
&quot;Healing&quot;,
&quot;Help&quot;,
&quot;Helping&quot;,
&quot;Letting Go&quot;,
&quot;Reaching Out&quot;,
&quot;Growth&quot;,
&quot;Growing&quot;,
&quot;Eternity&quot;,
&quot;Rescuing&quot;,
&quot;Saving&quot;,
&quot;Inspiration&quot;,
&quot;Inspiring&quot;,
&quot;Hope&quot;,
&quot;Flourishing&quot;,
&quot;abilities&quot;,
&quot;determination&quot;,
&quot;focus&quot;,
&quot;resolve&quot;,
&quot;will&quot;,
&quot;culture&quot;,
&quot;Variety&quot;,
&quot;Maintaining&quot;,
&quot;Breathing&quot;,
&quot;breath&quot;,
&quot;oxygen&quot;,
&quot;lungs&quot;,
&quot;Reminding&quot;,
&quot;Existence&quot;,
&quot;Divinity&quot;,
&quot;the Divine&quot;,
&quot;Allowing Me the Chance to Love&quot;,
&quot;the Possibility of Being Able to Be Thankful and Grateful and Appreciative!&quot;,
&quot;the Possibility of Being Able to Be&quot;,
&quot;Capability&quot;,
&quot;Appreciation&quot;,
&quot;Thankfulness&quot;,
&quot;Thanks&quot;,
&quot;my Heart&quot;,
&quot;heart&quot;,
&quot;Soul&quot;,
&quot;Connection&quot;,
&quot;Reconnection&quot;,
&quot;Opening&quot;,
&quot;Reopening&quot;,
&quot;Keeping&quot;,
&quot;Patience&quot;,
&quot;Forgiveness&quot;,
&quot;Forgiving&quot;,
&quot;Humility&quot;,
&quot;Surrender&quot;,
&quot;Clarity&quot;,
&quot;Seeing&quot;,
&quot;Sight&quot;,
&quot;Vision&quot;,
&quot;Hearing&quot;,
&quot;Sound&quot;,
&quot;Discretion&quot;,
&quot;Virtue&quot;,
&quot;Support&quot;,
&quot;Transmuting&quot;,
&quot;Granting&quot;,
&quot;Sustenance&quot;,
&quot;Faith&quot;,
&quot;Joy&quot;,
&quot;Expression&quot;,
&quot;Expressing&quot;,
&quot;Health&quot;,
&quot;Healthiness&quot;,
&quot;Choosing Love&quot;,
&quot;Contemplation&quot;,
&quot;Interpretation&quot;,
&quot;Reality&quot;,
&quot;Perfection&quot;,
&quot;Gratitude&quot;,
&quot;Gratefulness&quot;,
&quot;Grace&quot;,
&quot;Strength&quot;,
&quot;Strengthening&quot;,
&quot;Bravery&quot;,
&quot;You&quot;,
&quot;All that is&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to walk, to stand, to grow&quot;,
&quot;All that You have Created&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Rise with the sun&quot;,
&quot;Progress&quot;,
&quot;Good things&quot;,
&quot;Empathy&quot;,
&quot;Productivity&quot;,
&quot;a Beautiful, Perfect, Gorgeous Day&quot;,
&quot;Revelation&quot;,
&quot;Realization&quot;,
&quot;Being&quot;,
&quot;Light in my Heart&quot;,
&quot;Purity&quot;,
&quot;Essence&quot;,
&quot;Source&quot;,
&quot;Christ&quot;,
&quot;Christening&quot;,
&quot;this Precious Gift of Life&quot;,
&quot;this Insightful Revealing Insight&quot;,
&quot;this profound Insight&quot;,
&quot;these lessons&quot;,
&quot;this Glorious celebration&quot;,
&quot;Showing me&quot;,
&quot;Interesting Ways&quot;,
&quot;Showing me how to operate as a human Being&quot;,
&quot;moving me towards these amazing possibilities&quot;,
&quot;Showing me this Value!&quot;,
&quot;these Connections&quot;,
&quot;this Power&quot;,
&quot;this Creation&quot;,
&quot;these Rising Crescendos&quot;,
&quot;these Wonderous Changes&quot;,
&quot;this Openness&quot;,
&quot;the Chance to Love&quot;,
&quot;this Safety&quot;,
&quot;this Security&quot;,
&quot;this Stability&quot;,
&quot;these Blessings&quot;,
&quot;this Renewal&quot;,
&quot;this Greatness&quot;,
&quot;this Wealth&quot;,
&quot;these Rivers&quot;,
&quot;this Body&quot;,
&quot;the Highest State of Reality&quot;,
&quot;Spontaneity&quot;,
&quot;the Maker energy&quot;,
&quot;masculinity&quot;,
&quot;femininity&quot;,
&quot;balance&quot;,
&quot;Wholeness&quot;,
&quot;the Source&quot;,
&quot;the Silence&quot;,
&quot;the Currents of Flow&quot;,
&quot;the Awareness&quot;,
&quot;All&quot;,
&quot;Blessing my Life&quot;,
&quot;Always Carrying me&quot;,
&quot;Bringing me back into the next Divine Perfect Moment of Eternity&quot;,
&quot;Working Through me&quot;,
&quot;not abandoning me in the night&quot;,
&quot;pushing and pulling me forward&quot;,
&quot;Showing me signs&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to learn&quot;,
&quot;Leading me into Creation&quot;,
&quot;Amazing Creative Freedom&quot;,
&quot;this Open Heart, Full of Love and Expansion&quot;,
&quot;Moving me Forward&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Write&quot;,
&quot;Endless Inner Truth Expressed and Experienced&quot;,
&quot;Ecstasy&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Grow&quot;,
&quot;rescuing me from the darkness&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me better ways&quot;,
&quot;making me a Creative&quot;,
&quot;this Restoration&quot;,
&quot;this Art&quot;,
&quot;Blessing me financially&quot;,
&quot;Real Value&quot;,
&quot;this Creative Flow&quot;,
&quot;Showing me what matters&quot;,
&quot;Taking Care of me&quot;,
&quot;Arising in me&quot;,
&quot;Keeping me Connected&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Witness the Beauty&quot;,
&quot;this pen&quot;,
&quot;a song&quot;,
&quot;a dance&quot;,
&quot;gifts&quot;,
&quot;freedoms&quot;,
&quot;music&quot;,
&quot;Sound&quot;,
&quot;sleep&quot;,
&quot;Showing Me the Way back&quot;,
&quot;Keeping me on a beautiful path&quot;,
&quot;Helping me make the Right choices&quot;,
&quot;Being Patient with me and Helping me be Patient with myself&quot;,
&quot;granting the ability to transmute darkness into light&quot;,
&quot;the Light Upon the Hill&quot;,
&quot;this Calm&quot;,
&quot;this Still&quot;,
&quot;the Perfect&quot;,
&quot;Perfection&quot;,
&quot;the Wondrous&quot;,
&quot;the light of Christ Jesus&quot;,
&quot;this Peace&quot;,
&quot;the Beautiful Day&quot;,
&quot;the sacred moment&quot;,
&quot;Helping me believe that I am deserving of Blessings&quot;,
&quot;Helping me feel Deserving of Blessing&quot;,
&quot;Blessing me&quot;,
&quot;Supporting me&quot;,
&quot;Freeing me&quot;,
&quot;Sustaining me&quot;,
&quot;Keeping me from harm&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to walk in Kindness&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to have riches&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me Who I Am&quot;,
&quot;these unforeseen Blessings&quot;,
&quot;Prospering this Life&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Live without pride&quot;,
&quot;Giving me Good Intentions&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to reach out to others&quot;,
&quot;Helping me Create a Better Reality with Thought and Love&quot;,
&quot;this Awakening&quot;,
&quot;Granting me Hope&quot;,
&quot;Granting me Faith&quot;,
&quot;Ambition&quot;,
&quot;Eyes&quot;,
&quot;Ears&quot;,
&quot;skin&quot;,
&quot;Water&quot;,
&quot;Earth&quot;,
&quot;the Smooth&quot;,
&quot;the Flow&quot;,
&quot;hills&quot;,
&quot;Ripples&quot;,
&quot;Streams&quot;,
&quot;vineyards&quot;,
&quot;Fruits&quot;,
&quot;the heavens&quot;,
&quot;Heaven&quot;,
&quot;the Endless Skies Above&quot;,
&quot;Heaven on Earth&quot;,
&quot;the sunrise&quot;,
&quot;Sunlight&quot;,
&quot;the Moonlight&quot;,
&quot;the Ocean&quot;,
&quot;clear crystaline waters&quot;,
&quot;the Father&quot;,
&quot;the Mother&quot;,
&quot;the Son&quot;,
&quot;the Holy Spirit&quot;,
&quot;Loving Beings&quot;,
&quot;Angels&quot;,
&quot;Truth&quot;,
&quot;food&quot;,
&quot;my life&quot;,
&quot;my soul&quot;,
&quot;your life&quot;,
&quot;your soul&quot;,
&quot;humanity&quot;,
&quot;Solace&quot;,
&quot;Blessing every part of my Life&quot;,
&quot;this beautiful divine Glorious Abundant Prosperous Magical Blessed Fulfilled Peaceful Loving Day&quot;,
&quot;making me Amazing&quot;,
&quot;Restoring my and Flourishing my sensuality and sexuality&quot;,
&quot;turning my Focus Towards the Love of Creation&quot;,
&quot;Replacing my fear of other with Strength, Power, Humility, Surrender, Love, Joy, Goodwill, Blessing for others&quot;,
&quot;Healing and Warmth and real Peace and Comfort Inside and Making Me Whole&quot;,
&quot;Connecting me to Nature and Beauty and Life&quot;,
&quot;Pouring Out my Heart, Your Heart, Out Onto the Entire Earth&quot;,
&quot;melting the old to bring the new&quot;,
&quot;Protecting me Through hardship and struggle and strife&quot;,
&quot;the Moving Ocean, More Abundant in Riches than Crystal Diamonds&quot;,
&quot;Changing me&quot;,
&quot;Staying with me&quot;,
&quot;Comforting me&quot;,
&quot;Your Trust&quot;,
&quot;Your Spirit&quot;,
&quot;Your Wonderous Abundance of All Good Things&quot;,
&quot;Filling my soul&quot;,
&quot;Showing me Beauty&quot;,
&quot;This&quot;,
&quot;this Hope and Faith and Trust to Stand on&quot;,
&quot;Restoring my Spirit&quot;,
&quot;Caring about me&quot;,
&quot;Guiding My Life&quot;,
&quot;Restoring Me&quot;,
&quot;Making me this way&quot;,
&quot;Radiance&quot;,
&quot;Watering my Gardens with Fresh Springs&quot;,
&quot;my cup overflows&quot;,
&quot;Always Being With me&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Hold Onto what is Precious&quot;,
&quot;Filling Every Moment with So Much! So Much Unfathomable Greatness and Life and Meaning and Truth&quot;,
&quot;Opening my eyes to this Precious Perfect Moment in Eternity&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Confide in Your Embrace&quot;,
&quot;Setting my eyes on that which You Love&quot;,
&quot;Creating me to Be a Being that Loves what You Love&quot;,
&quot;Showing me how to walk&quot;,
&quot;blessing me in truth&quot;,
&quot;my Clarity of Speech&quot;,
&quot;this Renewal of Mind, Soul, Body, Spirit&quot;,
&quot;the Hidden Depths&quot;,
&quot;the Secret Beauties and Treasures&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Have this Love for You I so desperately needed&quot;,
&quot;Making All Things Possible for me&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me how to Trust You in my Heart and Soul&quot;,
&quot;Allowing Have Safety and Trust in Rest&quot;,
&quot;Restoring my Mind&quot;,
&quot;Teaching Me to Appreciate You and Blessing at Every Level of my Life&quot;,
&quot;Turning my Focus to Divine Love&quot;,
&quot;Revealing my Authenticity&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me to Find Treasure hidden in the depths of my soul&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me How to Establish a Relationship with my Heart&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Access Wisdom and Higher Meaning&quot;,
&quot;Strengthening me from Within&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me How to Change, How to Let Go, How to Be&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me How to Calm the Storms in my soul&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to Live in a world in which others desire to See and Hear me&quot;,
&quot;Making me Wealthier than I could Imagine&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me how to Cultivate a Garden of Thought in the mind&quot;,
&quot;Teaching me how to Drink from the Rivers and Waters and Springs&quot;,
&quot;Let this Love Penetrate Through my Existence&quot;,
&quot;the Sacred Word&quot;,
&quot;Allowing me to fall in Love with Love itself&quot;
]

function start(){
    passout = randoms();

    if (passout == &quot;&quot;) {
      passout = &quot;my Cup Overflows&quot;;
    }
    else {
      return passout;
    }
  }
//}
function randoms() {
  function randomGetNumber() { //generate a random number for array
    var randNum = Math.floor(1 + Math.random() * wordList.length);
    var randNumNum = randNum - 1;
    return randNumNum;
  }
  sendword = randomGetNumber()
  let returnedword = wordList.splice(sendword, 1); // get array value and delete entry
  if (!Array.isArray(wordList) || !wordList.length) { //when the array empties return Love
    returnedword = &quot;Love&quot;;
  }
  return returnedword;
}

function words() { // write sentence
  pre = &quot;Thank You for &quot;;
  word = start();
  and = &quot; and &quot;;
  wordtwo = start();
  wordthree = start();
  post = &quot;!&quot;;
  out = pre + word + and + wordtwo + and + wordthree + post;
  return out;
}
function fire() {
  $(&quot;#outputhtml&quot;).text(words()); //write to html
};

&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">So You Want To Be Famous</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/fame" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So You Want To Be Famous" /><published>2021-06-07T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-06-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/So-You-Want-to-Be-Famous</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/fame">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/fame&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/unused-energy-17.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;!-- 17 --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fame has been on the mind ever since realizing that Dorothy Parker was friends with F. Scott Fitzgerald who was friends with Ernest Hemingway.
These were amazing people for sure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What exactly was unique about these three amazing folk that made them famous?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing. They were living their lives and creating like millions of other talented artists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why they are famous is because Scott Fitzgerald incidentally created American propaganda, The Great Gatsby, depicting an American dream.
Politics, the US government, made these artists as widely known as gospel, taught in every school in the country. This is not success as we imagine it, rather this is business as usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fame we want and picture, to be known and seen by the world, it isn’t real. You are as famous as to the extent you live out your life in your world.
You are as famous as to the amount you express yourself in your world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again with Dorothy, Scott, and Hemingway, this was a clique, a group of friends. Remember when you were in high school? And there were different groups of students? There was certainly an elitist group amongst the groups. If you weren’t in that group, you likely did not want to be. You did not want to be like those people. Fame is that elitist group. It’s just a group. It isn’t a metric to success. That group in high school may have had a connection to the school newsletter. This is the same as the famous group in our society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a group of people that are famous in mainstream media simply because they are in that group. This group is no more or less than any other group of people in the world. They are no more or less qualified to be famous. It just so happens that one group is connected to infrastructure set up to broadcast their existence to millions of internet connected devices. There is no qualification for this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even when we understand this, some of us still want to be famous. Even when we know that fame is not success, some of us still want to be famous. Even when fame isn’t real, we still want it. Even when we understand that success is not real (different subject), we still want it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We still want fame because other people still believe that fame is the measure of success, because we would like to impress them and make them proud by achieving fame.
Is this a grave mistake? To achieve fame, does this not teach the wrong lesson to the eyes of all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does this not teach that others did something wrong to not achieve this fame, that they couldn’t figure out ‘the secret’ to fame (hint: there isn’t one), that they weren’t worthy of being seen or heard, acknowledged and valued?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Generating Receptivity</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/Receptivity" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Generating Receptivity" /><published>2021-05-24T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-05-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Generating-Receptivity</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/Receptivity">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Receptivity&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/duality.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;a href=&quot;/Receptivity&quot;&gt; ![image](/img/unused-energy-11.gif) &lt;/a&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen genuinely and others will desperately desire to genuinely hear you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah this sounds all nice and all but when none of us know how to do this, it doesn’t really help much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well as it turns out, some people do know how to use this and it’s quite the lucrative
skill to have in your arsenal. Add the skills to your life that improve your quality of life and you have
effectively changed your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This skill is relatively new. No one person holds every piece to it. The one who can learn this can
take the gold from available sources of information. If you learn this,
you are among the few people in this world to even know that this superpower exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- If you learn this,
you are among the few people in this world that even know that this superpower exists. --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;==== == ====&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;1&quot;&gt;1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening is the Golden Key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommend watching at 2x speed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;background-image: url(/img/r11.jpg)&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/saXfavo1OQo&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;2-reflective-power-&quot;&gt;2 Reflective Power &lt;!-- &lt;br&gt; (__if you watch only one video, watch this video__) --&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommend watching at 2x speed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;background-image: url(/img/r4.jpg)&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/A343tlP5iUA&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;3--achieve-authenticity&quot;&gt;3  Achieve Authenticity&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not being who you want to be, it’s being who you are. &lt;br /&gt;
If you are seen and heard, they can be seen and heard.
&lt;!--
Develop the courage to speak your mind by telling all your heart,
 to be imperfect. --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommend watching at 1.75X speed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;background-image: url(/img/r5.gif)&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/X4Qm9cGRub0&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;4-master-presence&quot;&gt;4 Master Presence&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pause and accept one’s reality to learn and communicate with them.
Allow life to flow through you and life becomes magic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommend watching at 1.75X speed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;background-image: url(/img/r6.jpg)&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Yq5pJ0q3xuc&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;additional-keys&quot;&gt;Additional Keys&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Decimate Shame - Brene Brown&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Embrace Accountability. &lt;br&gt;
Guilt is, &quot;I'm sorry, I made a mistake.&quot; &lt;br&gt; Shame is, &quot;I'm sorry, I am a mistake.&quot; --&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/psN1DORYYV0&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using Empathy - Brene Brown&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/1Evwgu369Jw&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;!--
Listening Tools &lt;br&gt;
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cSohjlYQI2A

Listening to the cries of the world and understanding with compassion is possible.
Receptive presence is possible.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jXWGs-QOZhE
--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something About You - Elderbrook &amp;amp; Rudimental&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;242&quot; height=&quot;242&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/N1EhXF1lskA&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;!--
captures the important piece being established,
the display of vulnerability by doing something with an unknown result and no expectation, risking potential rejection,
makes you present and authentically there and therefore seen and heard,
then others will also rise to meet their need of feeling seen and heard,
and you've now established trust
--&gt;
&lt;!--
Henry Rollins Talks About His Good Friend Joe Cole
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-OWiEzip9yU
--&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Emotional Alchemy</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/emotionalalchemy" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emotional Alchemy" /><published>2021-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Emotional-Alchemy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/emotionalalchemy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/emotionalalchemy&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/formless.webp&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emotional alchemy is an active experience that involves the changing or perhaps, the transmutation of one’s own feelings. This can lead to an entirely different life experience, in which the phrase, ‘never a dull moment’ becomes an increasingly exciting reality. For the experienced alchemist, life shifts to a chain of reliefs and joys, in some cases where there is hardly time to prepare for the next bombshell of bliss or satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often use the term ‘Shadow Work’ to refer to a part of this practice, as the parable of riding off into the darkness of night, only to return as the prodigal son coming home to his kingdom, having been restored with more light than before is a drama commonly understood in Carl Jung’s model of the Shadow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether we use emotional alchemy or not, we all are subjected to this experience of darkness to light in life, regardless of our desire to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should not expect to understand everything I describe here, as the feeling-based reality and operations within it do not translate well into the spoken word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My effort here is to write a universal abstract on the topic. This reading may seem nonlinear, as it is, emotional alchemy is not linear. There are many entrances from which to start understanding it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I will describe as emotional alchemy is not a formulaic process, such as physical alchemy, this is an evolving process of active and changing refinement, easier and more rewarding as the person becomes more equipped and aware of their own experience, such as the ability to catch and recognize antiquated thought patterns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also no question that this experience will always be relative to the individual, one person’s methodology and understanding of this will be vastly different than another’s. One person’s tool will likely not be accessible to another. A person with a background of mindfulness will also likely have a more effective experience than the person who is currently consumed by and overwhelmed with thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Emotional alchemy at its core starts with observing emotions that are present. Most of these recurring emotions are painful, so a core part of this process is a willingness to embrace some level of pain or discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my personal experience, the difference between facing emotional pain and running from that emotional pain is negligible. My experience is that facing an emotion is about 10% more painful than living with it. It is in the resolution of feeling, or changing of feeling, or releasing of feeling that is rewarding to many degrees, so it could be said that the reason to pursue emotional alchemy is that it is a continually rewarding experience, where many treasures can be found in one’s own soul.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This process of facing emotion is subtly different from being consumed by emotion, in the former, one retains an intention and focus to grow, change, and heal, in the latter, one is desiring to explore the depth of that feeling and drown in it. It takes time to begin to recognize the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Facing emotion is only possible from a positive and self-supportive headspace, most effective when operating from the role of mentally acting as an ‘inner consoler’, one who has an intention to give grace and compassion to oneself and console their own troubled feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When this topic is thought up, thoughts usually arise that, “I don’t have an inner world like that” or “I’m not that deep” or “That’s too complicated for me”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find these thoughts to be untrue when explored, as, at its core, this process is nothing more than having an intention and being a being that has emotions, both of which would describe all people. Like many activities, this process is as easy as attempting to try, again and again. Our greatest resource in this area is time, with which at every moment regardless of what we are doing, we are experiencing emotion, and have a chance to try to work with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those that have not focused on emotions in many years, it becomes more difficult to identify one’s feelings as they become unrecognizable as feelings. This is the case in which one feels that they “feel nothing”, or they “don’t feel anything”, or they feel “an absence of feeling”, or even “the absence of an absence of feeling”, all of which are deep spaces of actual feelings that can be worked with once identified as such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most difficult subject of course is the individual who has become obsessed with feeling great at all times, the one who will feel the most despair when they crash. This person is just as much feeling great as they are running as far as they can from all negative and painful reminders of feelings to the point of avoidance of themselves and others in their lives in order to escape the darkness of night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way emotions are approached varies circumstantially. There are so many methods of this alchemy, that it is likely you already actively use at least one in your daily life, and will naturally pick up more as you get older. It could be said then that what I am referring to are methods of advanced emotional alchemy.
The introduction to these methods is simply that you do not know which ones will work for you at this time in your life unless you try them, just as in physical alchemy, this is a process of experimentation and exploration. Think of this as a recipe cookbook, you can try to cook some, or add some recipes to your existing concoctions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A methodology as follows,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;1-asking-questions&quot;&gt;1 Asking questions.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asking yourself questions about what you are feeling, how you are feeling, why you are feeling, is a way to dig into the roots of emotion. In this process, you are removing your existing conclusions and reasons for why you feel this way. You are abandoning what you already have concluded, which is often what you have believed for many years.
A second line of questioning is often the next step, asking, “What am I missing?”, “What am I not seeing here?”, “What is a different way to interpret what I am experiencing?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;2-identifying-emotional-desires-and-needs&quot;&gt;2 Identifying emotional desires and needs.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is usually the case that a persistent negative emotion is tied to a core need that has long since gone unmet. You may already be familiar with some of these needs while unaware of how to access them or resolve them. Usually underneath “surface emotions” is a need to be seen and heard, a need to be loved, or a need to be connected, amongst others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;21-identification-of-core-needs&quot;&gt;2.1 Identification of core needs&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you feel an emotion, you can often ask, “When have I felt this before?”. If you feel you are in a safe space, it is often that memory will surface. Unlike therapy that seeks to identify memories and resolve them in an endless rabbit hole that will certainly never end, we’re simply trying to identify the need here. Oftentimes, a memory surfacing is enough to reveal what kind of emotion has been covered up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever cried and felt horribly toxic and disgusting afterward? We tend to avoid wanting to feel this way. I believe it works something like this. We once had an unmet need, then we formed a conclusion, a belief of why that need went unmet, and that belief covered over a space inside us, a space in which that need was meant to be filled with wonderful emotion. That belief became a shield around that space, and inside that space, a dark space without light grew the bitterness of lack. As we want to view ourselves in a positive standing and capable way, we unknowingly must avoid feeling whatever toxic acid might have cultivated in these darker places. We do not want to be sickly, needy, desperate, lacking creatures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beliefs that grow, or more accurately, the lies that grow, are usually about ourselves or others, such as, “People don’t like me”, or “I am this way”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;22-resolution-of-needs&quot;&gt;2.2 Resolution of needs.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is almost no need to try to dissect and untangle a web of beliefs, as we can accurately assume that whatever beliefs are surrounding these emotions, are simply, lies. There is no need to sort through them and pick out good lies from bad. We can assume our beliefs about our emotions are untrue. We can skip right over a field of thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A conscious willingness to accept that it is time to let this go, or that you are now ready to face this emotion may be required. It is likely that you will feel and believe that for some reason, you do not deserve and are not worthy of having this need met.
If from here you have identified an unmet need, you can seek to resolve it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can ask yourself, “What would it feel like if I had this need met?”. So for example, if the need was to be loved and accepted, what would it feel like if you were loved and accepted?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are able to imagine this and continue focusing on how it feels to have this need met, you may be able to feel the emotional need you were seeking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Healing wounds of this kind are known to feel like healing water is being poured onto painful scars, burning them until they are erased and filling that space with something brand new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are unable to feel this need met, you can take a different approach. You can think about someone you care about, or even once cared about, a family member or close friend, someone that you wish only the best for and want them to be happy. Now imagine that they feel the way you feel or they have this unmet need that you have. If you are attempting this right now, spend some time focusing on this, do not rush ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you feel about that? If you would not want them to suffer in this way, how cruel are you being to yourself to allow yourself to suffer in this way?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, you can take the feelings you have toward this person, your desire for them to know how okay they are, how you want to be there for them in this, how you wish that they knew that you loved them, how you wish they felt, and look back at yourself. How could you not love yourself in this way?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Focus on meeting this desired emotional need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this still does not work and you are willing to continue working on this, continue breathing slowly and just focus on a wish for yourself for some peace, grace, safety, rest. The emotional space you are looking to resolve may open, or it may need more time to resolve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;23-identification-and-resolution-of-desires&quot;&gt;2.3 Identification and resolution of desires.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many negative emotions can grow in us when we are not careful and deeply desire to have what others have that we do not.
In this lacking space grows jealousy, contempt, and other painful emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, these desires are easier to identify than emotional needs. Unfortunately, these tend to be more active emotions, and we may have actively grown them from small seeds to large spaces of deep and painful emotion by now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start the resolution process, you can acknowledge that there simply is no such thing as lack. These again are beliefs of lack, an illusion of lack that is a lie. When you see in others what you desire, the reason why you desire it is because it is you. You are desiring to be you. You are desiring something inside yourself that wishes to be seen outside yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of this, you can look inside yourself and see that inside you is what you desire outside. It takes time, but you can learn to be accepting of this inside yourself and be seen for being this. In other words, the verification and evidence that you are this, is that you can see this inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being grateful and happy for others having gifts and blessing also helps dissolve some of what is in these emotional spaces, but this article is not to teach spiritual lessons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;24-cultivating&quot;&gt;2.4 Cultivating&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will find that you can resolve some emotions and not others. You will find that you can access emotions sometimes and be unable to open up other times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is, again, the process of emotional alchemy. This is emotional work, or, an emotional art, a practice of refinement. It takes time, care, delicacy, and skill to create a refined work, in the same way as your soul.
Keep this in mind. The level at which you are able to access emotions is directly related to how safe you feel. Taking care of your self, your mind, your body, (even your spirit), are all elements that factor into your emotional access. Just as the right conditions of temperature and climate are required for certain works, the atmosphere that you work in does matter.
Proving to yourself that you do care about yourself by taking actions that show you care about yourself will over time increase the amount of trust you have that you can be trusted to take care of yourself. The more you trust yourself, the more willing you will be to open up to vulnerable places inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Patience, self-compassion, and grace are necessary to cut yourself some slack and learn how to be easier and more nurturing to yourself. This can be difficult in a world that encourages you to do the opposite, teaching you incorrectly that productivity comes before peace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;25-abilities&quot;&gt;2.5 Abilities&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you can expect to eventually experience as you turn your focus onto your heart in this way over time, is that you gain an ability that was not accessible before. Becoming more mindful in this way, - which pairs well with mindfulness and focused attention on the breath -, is you will become aware of yourself. You will have access to a mental process that was unavailable before, one that can question your thoughts, question your heart, question your actions, question your desires all from the present, rather than as an afterthought to be reflected on after the fact. You begin to wake up from the dream. Being awake in this way grants you the ability to change, to shift your focuses, to reinterpret your life, to no longer act out of routine, or be enslaved by fears and an overstimulated mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having access to this ability can grant you even more trust in yourself, as you can trust yourself to be able to consciously deal with whatever comes in your life. This trust will again increase your sense of safety and allow more emotion to feel safe enough to rise to the surface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A second ability is gained as well. You may already have access to this if you are empathetic. In listening to your heart, and becoming aware of emotions inside you, you will also become aware of an emotional reality in your world. You will begin to develop a second sight from which the world will teach and show you many insights, revelations, and wisdom in your interactions every day. You will notice that these insights were perhaps always there, but you were not listening to them, your focus was too far away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;advanced-emotional-alchemy&quot;&gt;Advanced Emotional Alchemy&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that not all emotional states are inherently bad, even if undesirable, as it is known that for example, the pain of grief is close to love. Certain emotions like depression can at times even be feelings about the world itself.
Keep in mind that we cannot always change the way we feel or what we experience, but we can always consciously control how we respond and interpret what we are experiencing. Being overwhelmed is of course, overwhelming. But you can actually change how you experience being overwhelmed, where your focus is. This is much like the phrase, “It’s okay to not be okay.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of what you are learning to do is not simply mind games. You are learning to allow your deeper heart to lead and the better more intuitive thoughts that can arise from focusing on it to lead you, and all that is required is that allowing. That intention of allowing your heart to open to start. Then, allowing something else into the space. To do this, you have to surrender a bit of control, to allow what is “outside of you”, outside of your comprehension and mental understanding, your spirit, to come into your heart to heal it. You may not always have the ability to surrender your control, your willpower. Sometimes this can only be when your mind and body are weak and tired and low on their usual stubbornness and strength, or when pride is severely injured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin the process of injecting in new emotion, what you can control here is again your focus and intentions. After opening to a painful emotion, you direct your intention to focus on what is needed there as said earlier, or you introduce a foreign element. You set your intention to connecting to safety, or warmth, or light, or love, or kindness, or grace, or God, or Christ, or your divinity, or angels, or loved ones, or whatever unknown love might exist somewhere out there that wants to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You set your intention on it, you ask for it, you wait on it, you relax with a small measure of faith and trust, you be patient on it while focusing on your heart, and when you start to feel your heart opening, you breathe into it and let go and release your fears and resistance and let it penetrate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you become more familiar with better feelings, you can start to practice focusing on those better feelings and replacing the spaces in which negative ones reside. Just experiment with it, you have every moment for the rest of your entire life to practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, what about raw pain? How do we transmute just pain? We don’t. Like many emotions we open up to it to allow it to dissolve quickly, to find that underneath that pain is the warmth of love. It’s like opening up a box of food and expecting birds to come down from the sky and take the food. You open it up, and allow it to work through its natural process and transform itself into love and leave. Pain is a lead that transmutes into gold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that fear is not an emotion to be transmuted. Fear is what will attempt to turn your heart cold to keep you from accessing your emotions. Its partner, doubt, is skilled at convincing you that you ought to not even try. Fear loses its hold in the presence of trust, and where is fear to be found when you feel safe and loved?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With love always,
James Bytes
2021&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Updater</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/rawrtheupdater" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Updater" /><published>2021-05-18T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-05-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/The-Updater</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/rawrtheupdater">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/rawrtheupdater&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/flowenergy.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;!-- {:class=&quot;img-responsive&quot;} --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The definitive way to watch your crypto assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sorcerawr.com/theupdater2&quot;&gt;The Updater 2&lt;/a&gt; - price info&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sorcerawr.com/theupdater&quot;&gt;The Updater&lt;/a&gt; - expanded info&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you make easy and simple gains, friend.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scripture Entropy</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/entropy" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scripture Entropy" /><published>2021-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-05-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Scripture-Entropy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/entropy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/entropy&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/universe.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;!-- {:class=&quot;img-responsive&quot;} --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scripture Entropy uses your word as entropy in a rog to generate scripture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sorcerawr.com/scriptureentropy&quot;&gt;Scripture Entropy&lt;/a&gt; - Fixed Entropy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sorcerawr.com/scriptureentropy2&quot;&gt;Scripture Entropy 2&lt;/a&gt; - Additional Entropy&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crypto Percents</title><link href="https://sorcerawr.com/trades" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crypto Percents" /><published>2021-05-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-05-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://sorcerawr.com/Crypto-Percents</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sorcerawr.com/trades">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/trades&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/img/crypto.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;!-- {:class=&quot;img-responsive&quot;} --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/7cooh1IEHC8fXqsiCF25IF&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;80&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; allow=&quot;encrypted-media&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Calculate percentages on your trades below&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://trinket.io/embed/python/cacd689c48?outputOnly=true&amp;amp;runOption=run&amp;amp;start=result&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard link:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://jamesbytes.trinket.io/sites/cryptopercentz&quot;&gt; CryptoPercentz &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;additional-links&quot;&gt;Additional Links&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  - TOP DEFI PICKS - &lt;a href=&quot;https://ndx.holdings/&quot; class=&quot;rainbow-text&quot;&gt;  NDX.HOLDINGS &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Bytes</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>